Please, man of God, help me!
Without this injection, I cannot walk.
I am tired of tablets and injections.
Please, help me, man of God!
Please, I have had operations nine times; next month will be the tenth time.
Please, I am tired.
This is what is in my leg.
Please, man of God, help me!
After a few years, they will take it out; they have to fix it in the other leg.
This is what is in my leg.
This is the injection I take before I can walk.
These are the tablets I am taking every day.
I have had operations nine times.
Man of God, help me, please!
Next month, I am booked for an operation.
Please, help me!
Prophet T.B. Joshua offers spirit-filled prayer.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer At The SCOAN Thursday Prayer Line
Stand up!
A divine utterance from Heaven is given and a divine operation has taken place.
Walk gently!
Go!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer At The SCOAN Thursday Prayer Line
Thank You, Jesus!
To God be the glory.
Mrs Joy Gersak is delivered and healed.
TESTIMONY TIME
Right now, the very lady in question is here in our midst to share her wonderful testimony.
We can already see the transformation; it is so clear.
We want to hear from her right now, to the glory of God.
Madam, you are very welcome, in Jesus' name.
Can you please introduce yourself to us and the lady beside you?
Emmanuel!
(God Is With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Joy Gersak.
I am from Austria.
I thank God.
Everybody should help me to thank God for bringing me back to life.
I was really suffering.
I was passing through pain from one operation to another.
Every day – tablets, doctors and from one doctor to another.
They said that it was sports – because of sports was why I had the pain.
I woke up one day and saw my leg was swollen.
They had to rush me to hospital.
On getting there, they said it was this and that.
They didn't really know what was happening to me.
They were saying that it was knee arthritis or pus.
I went from one doctor to another.
I took more than 13 tablets every day.
I was confused until the last operation, the ninth operation.
The ninth one is where they fixed in iron; everybody can still see it.
This is it.
This is the tenth one; they said they wanted to fix in more iron.
This is where they were draining water from.
It was my sister from Canada; God bless her.
She is the one who paid for my ticket to come to this place.
When I arrived here...
OK, before you go ahead madam...
We can see our sister is so overwhelmed by the wonderful testimony she has to share.
We just want you to explain clearly; for how long were you having this bilateral knee arthritis?
Explain to us; you've mentioned injections, tablets...
On a daily basis, what was the type of pain you were in because of this problem?
The pain was unbearable.
I cannot even remember and I don’t want to remember.
I cannot.
I could not eat or sleep.
I had to take tablets before I went to bed.
Before I would get out of bed, I would take tablets.
What were the things you were completely unable to do because of all of this?
I could not walk; I stopped working.
I could not do anything my mates were doing.
Not really.
Sometimes even to go to the toilet...
This is my senior daughter.
With the junior ones, she had to take me to the toilet and take me back.
Imagine!
I was really passing through pain.
You said you had passed through how many operations before you came here?
Nine operations.
Nine operations; to the extent that even metal was inserted into one of your knees?
Yes.
They had told you that they wanted to insert metal in your other knee, before you came here?
Yes, and they said that I didn’t have the right to decide.
They had to decide for me.
So, they decided and fixed the date on November 6th for me to submit all the results for my blood and everything.
I came here on the 3rd of November.
How did you find out about The SCOAN?
You were at the very critical stage now, they wanted to operate your other knee and insert iron...
How did you come to be here?
It was a friend; she is more than a sister to me and is based in Canada.
She is the one who sponsored my coming to this place.
We thank God Almighty.
When you came here...
We witnessed on the screen the events that happened when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you.
Can you just describe to us exactly what happened, as the man of God began to pray?
As the man of God was praying for me, I passed out.
I cannot remember what was going on.
The only thing I heard was, "Get up and walk" and I started running.
That was the only thing I remember.
Well, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
When the man of God was praying, speaking in tongues, and your whole body was shaking and trembling;
you can't remember what happened?
Not at all.
The moment you heard the declaration, "Rise up and walk!", what happened?
I was free and was no longer feeling any pain.
I slept like a baby – no tablets and no injections.
Wow, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
There is a big change, very big.
Before, I could not walk or do what my mates were doing.
But after I returned, everything was OK.
I can do everything.
I also started working.
I work now, whereas before, I could not work.
I was on pension as a retiree.
When I went back to Austria, I went back to the doctor.
The doctor checked everything and said I was OK; so, I started working.
Now, I work.
Well, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You had mentioned madam that the doctors had earlier booked you for an operation.
When you went back to your country - Austria, what happened?
When I went back to Austria, I went to meet my doctor and told him I wanted to have an x-ray done, which I did.
When the doctor checked, he asked me what I had done with my leg.
I said, "This is God" and he said, "God? What is God?"
I told him that I had travelled to Nigeria to a church for prayer.
He said there was no God but I said, "There is God".
He said he could not find anything in my leg to operate on so they could not operate on it.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
This is the hospital which had told our sister that they would have to insert iron in her other knee
because of the severity of the arthritis she was in, but the same hospital checked an x-ray and confirmed
there was no more problem.
She didn't have to go for an operation.
I have not been taking tablets, injections, therapy or seeing doctors.
Thank You, Jesus!
For the glory of God; we just like you to demonstrate how you can now walk freely,
after the prayer you received.
Wow, this is someone that had to take injections just to be able to move about in a slow way.
We can see what she is doing right now.
How are you feeling, madam?
I'm feeling very OK now; I think I may still go back to sports!
Wow, thank You, Jesus Christ!
Let's put our hands together one more time for our Lord Jesus Christ.
Madam, we can see medical reports on the board here, as well as an x-ray.
OK, this is a medical report, where the doctor says that everything is fine with my leg.
I do not need any operation.
It is written here in German.
We thank Jesus Christ.
The medical report is actually written in German language, but our sister is explaining that doctors
had confirmed that she no longer needed to go for an operation on her other knee, as she had been
completely healed, to the glory of God Almighty.
We can also see once again the x-ray here.
Can you just show this to us, madam?
This is the x-ray for me left knee before.
This is the x-ray of my right knee, where they wanted to operate.
Now, everything is OK.
This is from where they were removing water before.
Since then, they have stopped draining water.
Before, they would drain water three times a week.
I don't have pain anymore.
This is indeed a mighty miracle and we give all the glory to our Lord Jesus Christ;
one more time, people of God, let's put our hands together for Jesus for rescuing our sister
and completely setting her free - we thank our Lord Jesus Christ.
Madam, now, that you are here today, you are living, walking, talking miracle to the testimony
of our Lord Jesus Christ;
what is your advice to viewers around the world?
My advice to everyone who is watching me now is that
when you have problems, please, don't lose hope; run to God.
I went to many places and spent money but I came here and the man of God did not take anything from me.
As I was going back, I know what he gave me.
He gave me many things, including Morning Water.
Everybody should help me thank the man of God.
My advice is that if you have problems, run to God.
This is where I found my peace.
This is where I will be coming always, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus Christ.
My name is Deborah.
This is my mother.
Before she came to the church, she was having so much pain.
My sister and I had to do the dishes; clean the house, do the laundry and help her through the day.
We were sad because we knew that she was in so much pain and we couldn't really help her.
It was just to do the dishes, laundry and housework, nothing else.
We couldn't take the pain away from her.
Your mother came to The SCOAN.
What were the changes, the transformation that you saw when she came back to Austria?
We saw that she could do the things that she couldn't do before.
She can walk long distances and do the shopping.
My sister and I can concentrate more on our studies and go out more often.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
My advice would be: everyone should believe; don't lose faith in God.
Thank You, Jesus.
We thank God Almighty for this wonderful miracle.
We pray that God would give both our sisters here the grace to continue maintaining
the wonderful thing they've received from Him and to make the Word of God a standard for their lives
and as they do so, we know, better is not good enough - the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.